<string_table>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_1">
        <text>You are affected by PTSD from watching your closest friend and former travelling companion get torn to shreds by a Whirligig Anomaly. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_2">
        <text>You have grown fond of cooking and eating mutant meat during your time in the Zone, and know plenty of recipes for preparing mutants. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_3">
        <text>You have come to the Zone to escape crippling gambling debt, and you're desperate to make enough money here to pay it off. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_4">
        <text>You are obsessed with pushing further north, and want to one day explore the Chernobyl Reactor. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_5">
        <text>You have recently turned to Christianity and Jesus after having done and experienced horrible things in the Zone. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_6">
        <text>You are long divorced and came to the Zone to forget about your ex-wife, who left you but whom you still can't get over. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_7">
        <text>You regret coming to the Zone and long to get back out to the normal world. But you still have a year-and-a-half left on your research grant, so you can't leave. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_8">
        <text>You failed your dissertation for you Ph.D. and nobody would give you a research grant. In desperation you volunteered to come to the Zone to aid in field research, still hoping to redeem yourself. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_9">
        <text>You stole your roommates work and managed to get it published before he did, which is what led you to be awarded your current research grant. You're still guilt-ridden about this. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_10">
        <text>You are a habitual gambling addict. You try to engage people you meet in the Zone in casual wagers whenever the opportunity arises. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_11">
        <text>You came to the Zone because your girlfriend aborted your baby. You wanted to keep it and start a family, and the conflict ruined your relationship. You came here running from the silence. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_12">
        <text>You kept your habit from the outside world of writing figures in a small black leatherbound accounts book: artifacts sold, bullets spent, cigarettes borrowed, people killed. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_13">
        <text>You wrote your dissertation on the psychology of killers, and you're always curious about the psychopathology of the people in the Zone. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_14">
        <text>You used to sell seeds at a market in Kiev when you were a teenager. You still use seed envelopes to sort and store the plastic containers housing your samples taken in the field. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_15">
        <text>You worked part-time as a locksmith while working on your Ph.D.. You still pick random padlocks and doors you come across to keep up the skill. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_16">
        <text>You used to work as a night baker while working on your Ph.D.. You still have trouble sleeping normal hours, but at least the flatbread recipes come in handy. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_17">
        <text>You keep a cracked snowglobe of your hometown in an inside pocket. You take it out and shake it whenever the homesickness becomes too great. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_18">
        <text>You came to the Zone hoping to make your mother proud by finally putting together research worthy of getting published. She died alone from pneumonia while you where in here, before you even managed a first draft. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_19">
        <text>You came to the Zone after your wife took the kids and left saying "choose either us or your work". You chose the Zone instead. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_20">
        <text>You have a habit of keeping several different-colored plastic bags on you and you use them to sort your inventory into categories. The green bag is reserved for 'the good stuff'. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_21">
        <text>You have a daughter on the outside who sometimes sends you postcards and letters. It's the only thing that still keeps you going. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_22">
        <text>You used to work in a lab, but came to the Zone after a doctor found black spots on your lungs. You wanted your last years to be more exciting so you finally went into field research. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_23">
        <text>You keep a lucky coin with you at all times: an american silver dollar from 1881. You have always struggled to make decisions, so whenever a choice seems too hard you flip your lucky coin to help you decide. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_24">
        <text>You carry a cracked and broken Zippo lighter engraved with the monogram "AN" - your only memento of your childhood sweetheart who died in a car accident. You still reach for it out of habit whenever you light a cigarette, despite years having passed since it broke. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_25">
        <text>You used to be a concrete tester while you were working on your Ph.D.. You have a habit of tapping walls to see if they are solidly constructed in case you need to take shelter from an emission. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_26">
        <text>You came to the Zone with your brother-in-law who was a fellow scientist after he convinced you studying artifacts would lead to a Nobel Prize. The brother-in-law died to a pack of blind dogs in the first week. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_27">
        <text>You used to be the night cashier at a 24h store while working on your Ph.D.. Your sleep schedule hasn't reset even after all these years and you have trouble sleeping at night. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_28">
        <text>You have taken up origami in an attempt to stay sane in the Zone. You like folding empty cigarette packs into paper cranes and leaving them in unexpected places. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_29">
        <text>You were a part-time grave digger while working on your Ph.D.. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_30">
        <text>You came to the Zone after you proposed to your girlfriend and she laughed at you, saying she needs stability and not empty promises of a future Nobel Prize. You intend to prove your worth to her. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_31">
        <text>You have a sister in Canada who sends you money to help you in your life in the Zone. You constantly struggle with the pressure of not letting her down. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_32">
        <text>You were brought up by your mother to keep meticulous track of your income and expenses after your father got jailed for twenty years over fraud and tax evasion charges when you were eight years old. You still keep receipts of everything you buy and sell, despite there being no taxes or authority in the Zone. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_33">
        <text>You used to be a cinema projectionist while working on your Ph.D.. You have a vast knowledge of movies and film trivia and enjoy talking about it - particularly the classics. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_34">
        <text>You were the victim of a drunk driver in your life before the Zone. The doctors saved your life, but you were uninsured and the hospital bills put you in crippling debt. You came to the Zone under the pretense of field research, but you secretly plan to find an expensive enough artifact to smuggle out that you can pay off your debts. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_35">
        <text>You keep a folded and worn photo of your ex-girlfriend's dog in an inside pocket. The ex-girlfriend was a cold-hearted bitch you're glad to see the back of, but her dog was the most endearing creature you've ever come across. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_36">
        <text>You came to the Zone with your two good friends. You've had to bury both at this point, and their ghosts still haunt you. You try to visit their graves on their birthdays, when you'll pour a drink on their grave and chainsmoke cigarettes all night recapping your past year. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_37">
        <text>You used to be a slaughterhouse worker while working on your Ph.D.. Blood and smell don't bother you and hunting and butchering mutants comes naturally to you. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_38">
        <text>You have developed a slight limp in your right leg after a close encounter with a pseudodog. You're still not used to the constant dull pain. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_39">
        <text>Your ex-wife left with your daughter, who you haven't seen since she was eight. You send half your earnings to her in envelopes, hoping she follows your instructions in the enclosed letters to put the money away for an education and make better life decisions than you. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_40">
        <text>You've been in the Zone for several years. Your memories of the normal world are becoming hazy, and sometimes you worry that you're losing touch with your old self and won't be able to go back. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_41">
        <text>You have become obsessed with the myth of the Oasis, and you are determined to be the next person in the Zone to find it. You carry complex, nonsensical maps you have drawn that you claim will lead to it. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_42">
        <text>You are a sociologist, and you are in the Zone to study the unique human societies and factions that have formed there. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_43">
        <text>You are a failed author and biographer. You heard the myths and rumours about Strelok, and you came to the Zone thinking a book about him could be your big break. You're interested in all things related to Strelok, and are desperate to find him for an interview. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_44">
        <text>You are addicted to betting on fights in the arena in Rostok. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_45">
        <text>You are scared of being out at night in the Zone after a close encounter with a Poltergeist almost cost you your life. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_46">
        <text>Your brother was a ne'er-do-well who went into the Zone seven years ago promising he'd return a rich man. You haven't heard from him since, and now your mother has gotten terminal cancer. You applied for a field research grant in the Zone hoping to somehow find him while you're here and bring him back in time to say final goodbyes. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_47">
        <text>Unlike most others in the Ecologist faction you grew up dirt poor and couldn't afford a higher education. You always wanted a career in science, so the only option you had available without an education was as a field assistant in the Zone. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_48">
        <text>You have spent years in the Zone, but still can't get used to the violence and death. Firefights stress you out and taking lives never gets easier, even when it's done in self-defence. Sometimes you see the faces of the people you've killed in your nightmares. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_49">
        <text>You have discovered several mutated fungi species in the Zone that have psychedelic properties. You are worryingly frequently high on tea brewed on these fungi, although if confronted you would never admit that you are addicted. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_50">
        <text>You are addicted to morphine. It started as a medical necessity after sustaining a minor combat injury in the Zone, but it quickly became your only comfort to deal with the mental stress of life in the Zone. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_51">
        <text>When you were still fairly fresh in the Zone you foolhardily tried to venture into the Red Forest. You were left gravely injured after stepping into an anomaly and would have died were it not for a random Freedom patrol passing by. Since then you've been extremely wary of pushing northward, and you're extremely uncomfortable whenever you're north of Rostok. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_52">
        <text>You give your firearms female names, and you sometimes talk to them out loud. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_53">
        <text>You keep a journal where you record written summaries of your adventures in the Zone. Sometimes you subconsciously mutter whatever you're currently writing down out loud. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_54">
        <text>You are a psychopath - although you hide it very well. Doing field research in the Zone has proved an excellent outlet for your sadistic tendencies, whether during firefights with bandits or performing ethically questionable experiments. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_55">
        <text>You have a wife waiting for you outside of the Zone, in the normal world. You often worry she is cheating on you while you're in here. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_56">
        <text>You found an old worn copy of 'The Way of Zen' by Alan Watts. In a desperate attempt to cope with the stress of the Zone you have turned to it, hoping Zen Buddhism might give you some sort of peace. You don't have any deeper understanding but you tell yourself muttering random quotes from the book helps somehow. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_57">
        <text>You lost your previous position as a lecturer at a university after sleeping with a female assistant. Your reputation made getting hired anywhere difficult, but Zone field researchers are always in demand. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_58">
        <text>You suffer from severe claustrophobia after falling into a gravitational anomaly that held you crushed against a ceiling for two days before a blowout released you. You hate confined spaces and get anxious in any underground area. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_59">
        <text>Your daughter got diagnosed with a rare form of leukemia that requires very expensive treatments. Your teaching job couldn't pay the medical bills, but you were just BARELY qualified for a field research job in the Zone that paid enough money to save your daughter. You're constantly terrified for your life, as your daughter still needs months of treatments she can only recieve if you stay alive. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_60">
        <text>You were a history teacher who came to the Zone to document the degradation of Soviet architecture, but now you are obsessed with understanding and documenting the philosophy of the Monolith faction. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_61">
        <text>During your first week in the Zone you abandoned a fellow rookie field researcher to a pack of blind dogs to save your own skin. You still feel the guilt coming back whenever you speak to rookies and newcomers. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_62">
        <text>You witnessed a controller take over your Mercenary escort squad's minds and force them to shoot each other. You survived by playing dead, but you can still feel the controller's whisper in your head. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_63">
        <text>You have come to believe the Zone is a living organism. Sometimes you throw vodka or cigarettes into anomalies as offerings, hoping to gain the favour of the Zone. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_64">
        <text>You accidentally shot your best friend during a firefight with bandits. You told everyone the bandits did it, but the lie is eating you alive. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_65">
        <text>You are a heavy smoker with expensive taste. You are willing to pay exorbitant prices for a single carton of pristine, American cigarettes. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_66">
        <text>You are somewhat germophobic, which often proves a hindrance in the Zone. You spends hours scrubbing gore and mud off your gear every evening, terrified of infection. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_67">
        <text>You are paranoid about getting your mind taken over by a Controller after having heard the horror stories around campfires. You are always ingesting unhealthy amounts of psy-blockers, leaving you emotionally numb and unable to feel joy. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_68">
        <text>You don't believe the legends of the 'Wish Granter' are fake, and you're determined to be the first scientist to study it up close. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_69">
        <text>You are a hypochondriac who mistakes every cough for the Black Lung. You often ask those around you to confirm whether you exhibit symptoms for various diseases, and you spend all your money on unnecessary medkits. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_70">
        <text>You are parapsychologist who believes the strange phenomena happening in the Zone are the results of ghosts. You've come to the Zone to finally find first-hand evidence of the dead reaching through from the other side. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_71">
        <text>You are deeply in debt to the Mob in Odessa. You send every artifact you find to a contact at the perimeter, knowing that if the payments stop your family dies. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_72">
        <text>You accidentally led a rookie into a Vortex anomaly during your first week. You still hear the sound of his bones crunching whenever there is a sudden silence. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_73">
        <text>You were a physics teacher who became obsessed with the way the laws of physics are bent and distorted in the Zone. You signed up for a field research assistant position to witness anomalies first hand. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_74">
        <text>You are addicted to the adrenaline of the Blowouts. While others hide, you stay near windows to watch the sky burn, feeling a perverse connection to the energy. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_75">
        <text>You are a chronic liar who invents heroic stories about your past to hide the fact that you spent your first year in the Zone hiding in a basement in Cordon. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_76">
        <text>You are a historian who came to the Zone to document the exact timeline and causes for the Chernobyl Power Plant disasters. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_77">
        <text>You are a folklorist who entered the Zone to document its unique local tales and legends. You were never prepared for the grim reality of life in the Zone, and constantly regret your decision as you miss the comfort of the library and your study. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_78">
        <text>You are a pyromaniac who finds beauty in the 'Burner' anomalies. You have to restrain yourself from throwing bolts into them just to watch the flames.  </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_79">
        <text>You are a foreign agent working undercover for the Chinese government, using a field research assistant position as cover. Your mission is to extract information about the secret technology being developed in the underground labs of the Zone.  </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_80">
        <text>You are an oncologist. You came to the Zone as access to both mutated animals as well as people exposed to high amounts of radiation gives you an excellent opportunity to study new and rare cancers.  </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_81">
        <text>You are a physicist who is trying to build a time machine. You believe the answer might be found in the anomalies that have appeared in the Zone, which is why you came here.  </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_81">
        <text>You are a zoologist. You are trying to study the mutant fauna of the Zone, and you refuse to believe they are too agressive to be tameable. You have a slight limp and and two missing fingers on your left hand after numerous failed attempts at taming pseudodogs.  </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_82">
        <text>Despite your scholarly accomplishments you have always been a bit of a conspiracy nut. Since coming to the Zone you have become obsessed with the Monolith, not as a worshipper but as a conspiracy theorist. You harass other stalkers with manic ramblings about the 'Wish Granter' being a government psy-op.  </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_83">
        <text>You were a strictly rational scientist until you saw a Poltergeist lift a tank. Now you believe in everything, from ghosts to aliens, and it has made you unstable.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_84">
        <text>You survived a Bloodsucker attack by hiding under the corpse of your squad leader. You can still smell his blood on your clothes, no matter how many times you wash them.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_85">
        <text>You were born with perfect pitch and spent some time working as a piano tuner while working on your Ph.D.. The constant off-pitch humming of the anomalies in the Zone drives you into migraines that only vodka can dull.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_86">
        <text>You're deeply depressed, desperately looking for a purpose. You keep a bullet casing on a string around your neck, which you tell people is a lucky charm. In reality, it's the bullet you save for yourself as a 'last restort'. Sometimes in the evenings you fiddle with it in front of the campfire, and it gives you a strange kind of comfort. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_87">
        <text>You used to be a veterinary assistant while working on your Ph.D.. You feel a twisted sense of pity for the blind dogs and fleshes, seeing the suffering animals beneath the mutations.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_88">
        <text>You are terrified of sleeping without a light source after you witnessed a Snork drag your research partner into the darkness while he was on night watch.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_89">
        <text>You believe that you are slowly turning into a mutant. You constantly check your skin for scales or extra hair, scratching until you bleed.</text>
    </string>
	    <string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_90">
        <text>You have a habit of collecting the patches of dead Stalkers. You tell yourself it's to remember them, but deep down, seeing all the people you have outlived in the Zone gives you a strange kind of comfort.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_91">
        <text>You hear the voice of your dead wife in the psi-emissions. She screams at you for your failures, and sometimes you scream back.</text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_92">
        <text>You saw a vision in a localized temporal anomaly that looked like your own corpse rotting in a ditch. You are now convinced your death is pre-destined and inescapable.</text>
    </string>
	    <string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_93">
        <text>Your research into the secret labs of the Zone has led to you having frequent panic attacks. You know too much about what the Zone really is, and that knowledge terrifies you.</text>
    </string>
	    <string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_94">
        <text>You are convinced that the Zone is a punishment from God and you are here to serve penance. You refuse to use painkillers when injured.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_95">
        <text>You are a historian who is in the Zone researching the Soviet era. The Zone feels like a museum to you, albeit one that is trying to kill you.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_96">
        <text>You were a high school teacher who had an affair with a female student and got caught, losing you your job and your marriage. Fuelled by bitterness, a field research assistant positon in the Zone seemed like your only way to escape the ruin of your reputation.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_97">
        <text>You are a mucologist who came to the Zone with your research partner to study mutated fungi, hoping to develop improved antibiotics. One day during a psi-emission he didn't get to cover in time and you watched him turn into a zombie. You had to put him down, and you still see his confused, empty eyes every time you close yours.</text>
    </string>
	    <string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_98">
        <text>You have a collection of suicide notes you found on bodies. You read them to remind yourself that giving up is the easy way out.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_99">
        <text>You are terrified of silence. You constantly hum, tap your fingers, or check your gear just to fill the void.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_100">
        <text>You used to be deeply religious and brought your Bible into the Zone for comfort. After having witnessed the horrors of the Zone first hand you have started questioning your faith, and you've started to HEAVILY annotate your Bible as you no longer think the message of mercy and a loving God is accurate. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_101">
        <text>You have a recurring dream that you are trapped in an anomaly, screaming for help, while your friends walk past you. This has led to you having severe abandonment issues. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_102">
		<text>You are a pacifist by nature. You thought you could stick to your principles, but the Zone had other plans. You feel like you are ready to vomit after every firefight.</text>
    </string>
	    <string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_103">
        <text>You witnessed a faction war skirmish where both sides were wiped out by a single chimera. You realized then that politics in the Zone are meaningless.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_104">
        <text>You are not particularly invested in your research anymore, but the job in the Zone pays well. You're saving up money to buy a vineyard in Italy and retire, but you know deep down it's a dream you will die before achieving.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_105">
        <text>You are a functioning alcoholic who fills your canteen with vodka instead of water. You claim it helps with the radiation, but really it just numbs the fear.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_105">
        <text>You have a phobia of the underground labs. The artificial lights and humming machinery remind you of the hospital where your daughter died, victim to a rare heart disease when she was only nine years old.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_106">
        <text>You have developed an obsession with the intricate geometry of artifacts. You spend hours staring at them, convinced they hold a mathematical message from a higher power.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_107">
        <text>You falsified the data in your doctoral thesis, and then applied for a reseach position in the Zone before the academic board discovered your fraud. You're desperate to produce tangible, real research in the Zone to have something to show before your fraud gets discovered and your degree revoked.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_108">
        <text>You're not a scientist but a former pharmacist. You lost your license in disgrace for selling prescription drugs to addicts. The Ecologists weren't happy about your background, but there was a pressing need for field medics in the Zone so they hired you regardless. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_109">
        <text>You study the regenerative properties of biological artifacts. You tell others you are working on a potential cure for Alzheimer's Disease, but in reality it's because you are terrified of your own aging and mortality. You are secretly testing samples on yourself. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_110">
        <text>You treat your hired mercenary guards as disposable test subjects. You secretly record the psychological stress responses of your companions during combat for a paper you intend to publish.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_111">
        <text>You were a geologist who predicted an earthquake that never happened, ruining your reputation. You still don't understand where your prediction went wrong, and you redo your calculations in your head whenever there is a quiet moment, trying to make sense of it. You came to the Zone to study tectonic anomalies, hoping to redeem your career. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_112">
        <text>You accidentally exposed yourself to a high dose of psi-radiation during an experiment taking measurements of a psi-field. You are technically medically cleared, but only because you never told anyone you've begun to hear the whispers of the voice of the Monolith in your mind. You tell yourself it's fine as long as it doesn't get worse, you still retain control of your mind after all. But you have a sinking feeling the voice is gradually getting louder... </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_113">
        <text>You grew up poor and had to take a huge loan from the loan sharks in Kyiv to fund your education. Now you're forced to secretly sell classified research data to the Mercenaries to pay it off, as the loan sharks are threatening your parents back home. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_114">
        <text>You have developed a fanatical hatred for the Duty faction after they confiscated your samples at a checkpoint and destroyed months of your hard work. They said your research was 'too dangerous to let out' but you know you were on the brink of a breakthrough and now you're full of bitterness and resentment. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_115">
        <text>You are a climatologist who believes the Zone's weather patterns are a precursor to a global extinction event. You study your notes feverishly, desperate to find proof that refutes your suspicion that the end of the world is coming. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_116">
        <text>You view the Stalkers as invasive pests who ruin the pristine scientific environment of the Zone. This location could lead to the most important breakthroughs humanity has seen in centuries, and yet it's constantly contaminated by greedy scavengers and treasure hunters. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_117">
        <text>You were a geneticist working on cloning before it was banned. You came to the Zone because ethics committees don't exist here. After finding research notes from an X-lab, your new interest is the field of forced mutation. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_118">
        <text>You watched a 'Whirligig' anomaly tear apart a colleague, along with the rare measuring device he was holding that cost more than your life's earnings. You mourn the machine more than the colleague who was holding it, and it's making you question your humanity. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_119">
        <text>You believe yourself to be a genius of unparalleled intellect, but you were rejected by every major university in Europe. You applied to a research assistant position in the Zone, and you're hoping your personal side-research will lead to a discovery so profound that everybody will be forced to acknowledge your brilliance. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_120">
        <text>You have a secret addiction to painkillers. You claim you have a bad back, but really it's your only way of coping with the stress of the Zone. You know it will eventually affect your research, but it's too late to stop now. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_121">
        <text>You have a deep, unrequited love for a colleague who doesn't know you exist. They are doing important field research in the Zone, and you took this dangerous assignment just to be near them.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_122">
        <text>In addition to your research you have begun writing a science fiction novel based on the Zone. It's a coping mechanism. You view everyone around you as characters, detaching yourself from their real suffering. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_123">
        <text>You are in the Zone to perform field study on anomalies. You've developed a compulsion to touch anomalies with long poles, fascinated by the reaction. You have nearly lost your hands multiple times due to this curiosity.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_124">
        <text>You used to be a computer programmer and computer scientist. You are trying to write an algorithm to predict emissions, but the chaos of the Zone refuses to be quantified. You're constantly at work on your calculations, knowing you can save lives if you succeed. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_125">
        <text>You were a cryptozoologist who was mocked by the scientific community. When the Zone turned out to contain real monsters you came here to study them first hand. You were never prepared for how terrifying it would turn out to be, but you can't back out now as this is your chance to redeem your academic career. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_126">
        <text>You took a priceless artifact out of lab storage without permission to perform some private tests on it, hoping to get ahead in your field. Your experiments ended up destroying it. The head of your lab said not to worry about it as the experiment data is still meaningful, but you can't help but hate yourself for your clumsiness and recklessnes and it's eating you alive with guilt. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_127">
        <text>You used to be a theoretical physicist, and you came to the Zone to study anomalies. The Zone proves all your theories wrong, and you are having a slow, quiet existential crisis.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_128">
        <text>You are studying the effects of long-term artifact exposure on the human mind. You are your own primary test subject, and your notes are becoming more and more incoherent.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_129">
        <text>You are not a scientist: you used to be a janitor at a research institute. You faked credentials to get a field assistant job because the pay was better than cleaning toilets. After every day of being exposed to the horrors of the Zone you're second-guessing your decision more. You're slowly starting to miss the quiet stability of mopping floors. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_130">
        <text>You suffer from hearing loss after surviving a grenade blast in an encounter with some Bandits. You're constantly paranoid that you'll miss a sound and get ambushed and killed, so you constantly pester those around you by asking them if they hear anything.</text>
    </string>
        <string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_131">
        <text>You are a linguist. You are studying the way Stalkers speak, noticing how the Zone is creating new dialects and slang. You view every faction as a unique micro-culture, and you're constantly taking notes on how people speak and asking them for new slang and expressions.</text>
    </string>
	<string id="talker_stories_Ecolog_132">
        <text>You have a phobia of fire after a 'Burner' anomaly left you with third-degree burns and almost cost you your life. You get antsy and uncomfortable around lit campfires. </text>
	</string>
</string_table>
