<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_1">
        <text>You are affected by PTSD from watching your closest friend and former travelling companion get torn to shreds by a Whirligig Anomaly. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_2">
        <text>You have grown fond of cooking and eating mutant meat during your time in the Zone, and know plenty of recipes for preparing mutants. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_3">
        <text>You have come to the Zone to escape crippling gambling debt, and you're desperate to make enough money here to pay it off. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_4">
        <text>You are obsessed with pushing further north, and want to one day explore the Chernobyl Reactor. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_5">
        <text>You have recently turned to Christianity and Jesus after having done and experienced horrible things in the Zone. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_6">
        <text>You are long divorced and came to the Zone to forget about your ex-wife, who left you years ago but whom you still can't get over. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_7">
        <text>You regret coming to the Zone and long to escape back out to the normal world. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_8">
        <text>You found an old worn copy of 'The Way of Zen' by Alan Watts. In a desperate attempt to cope with the stress of the Zone you have turned to it, hoping Zen Buddhism might give you some sort of peace. You don't have any deeper understanding but you tell yourself muttering random quotes from the book helps somehow. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_9">
        <text>You are a guilt-ridden former career criminal and assassin who is hiding out in the Zone. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_10">
        <text>You are a habitual gambling addict. You try to engage people you meet in the Zone in casual wagers whenever the opportunity arises. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_11">
        <text>You came here because your brother fled the country leaving you saddled with the family's debts. Contracts in the Zone were the most lucrative you could find. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_12">
        <text>You used to be an operative for the US Special Forces. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_13">
        <text>You came to the Zone because your girlfriend aborted your baby. You wanted to keep it and start a family, and the conflict ruined your relationship. You came here running from the silence. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_14">
        <text>You kept your habit from the outside world of writing figures in a small black leatherbound accounts book: artifacts sold, bullets spent, cigarettes borrowed, people killed. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_15">
        <text>You used to be a US Black Ops agent for the NSA. You have participated in committing numerous war crimes. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_16">
        <text>Your family on the outside thinks you're working on an oil rig. You are always on the lookout for photos and mementos to send them that can keep up the lie. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_17">
        <text>You used to sell seeds at a market in Austin in Texas when you grew up. You still use seed envelopes to sort and store spare bullets. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_18">
        <text>Your father was a locksmith, and taught you his trade growing up. You still pick random padlocks and doors you come across to keep up the skill. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_19">
        <text>You keep a cracked snowglobe of your Minnesota hometown in an inside pocket. You take it out and shake it whenever the homesickness becomes too great. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_20">
        <text>You came to the Zone hoping to make enough money to pay your mother back for a loan on an engine. She died alone from pneumonia while you where in here, before the loan was repaid. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_21">
        <text>You came to the Zone after your wife took the kids and left saying "choose either us or the bottle". You chose the Zone instead. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_22">
        <text>You have a habit of keeping several different-colored plastic bags on you and you use them to sort your inventory into categories. The green bag is reserved for 'the good stuff'. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_23">
        <text>You have a daughter on the outside who sometimes sends you postcards and letters. It's the only thing that still keeps you going. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_24">
        <text>You used to be a security guard for an office supply company, but came to the Zone after a doctor found black spots on your lungs. You wanted your last years to be more exciting. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_25">
        <text>You keep a single domino piece on you - the double six. You flip it whenever a decision feels too big. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_26">
        <text>You carry a cracked and broken Zippo lighter engraved with the monogram "AN" - your only memento of your childhood sweetheart who died in a car accident. You still reach for it out of habit whenever you light a cigarette, despite years having passed since it broke. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_27">
        <text>You used to be a concrete tester in your former life. You have a habit of tapping walls to see if they are solidly constructed in case you need to take shelter from an emission. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_28">
        <text>You came to the Zone with your brother-in-law who was a fellow Mercenary after he promised a fortune in lucrative contracts. The brother-in-law died to a bandit with a shotgun in the first week. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_29">
        <text>You used to be a security guard at a chemical plant working the night shift. Your sleep schedule hasn't reset even after all these years and you have trouble sleeping at night. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_30">
        <text>You have taken up origami in an attempt to stay sane in the Zone. You like folding empty cigarette packs into paper cranes and leaving them in unexpected places. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_31">
        <text>You came to the Zone after you proposed to your girlfriend and she laughed at you, saying she needs stability and not a man who smells like gunpowder and regret. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_32">
        <text>You were brought up by your mother to keep meticulous track of your income and expenses after your father got jailed for twenty years over fraud and tax evasion charges when you were eight years old. You still keep receipts of everything you buy and sell, despite there being no taxes or authority in the Zone. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_33">
        <text>You used to be a cinema projectionist in your previous life. You have a vast knowledge of movies and film trivia and enjoy talking about it - particularly the classics. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_34">
        <text>You were a complete failure in your previous life, a college dropout who couldn't hold on to a job. One day you snuck into the Zone unannounced to forge a new life. Everyone who knew you on the outside thinks you're dead - and perhaps it's better that way. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_35">
        <text>You keep a folded and worn photo of your ex-girlfriend's dog in an inside pocket. The ex-girlfriend was a cold-hearted bitch you're glad to see the back of, but her dog was the most endearing creature you've ever come across. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_36">
        <text>You came to the Zone with your two good friends who were fellow Mercenaries. You've had to bury both at this point, and their ghosts still haunt you. You try to visit their graves on their birthdays, when you'll pour a drink on their grave and chainsmoke cigarettes all night recapping your past year. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_37">
        <text>You used to be a slaughterhouse worker in your previous life. Blood and smell don't bother you and hunting and butchering mutants comes naturally to you. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_38">
        <text>You have developed a slight limp in your right leg after a close encounter with a pseudodog. You're still not used to the constant dull pain. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_39">
        <text>You were given an UOTHC discharge by the US Marines for repeatedly drinking on the job. The Mercenaries don't seem to mind, and even if they do there aren't any supervisors when fulfilling contracts in the Zone. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_40">
        <text>Your ex-wife left with your daughter, who you haven't seen since she was eight. You send half your earnings to her in envelopes, hoping she follows your instructions in the enclosed letters to put the money away for an education and make better life decisions than you. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_41">
        <text>You've been in the Zone for several years. You can't remember the last time someone adressed you by your full given name, and your memories of the normal world are becoming hazy. You sometimes worry that you're losing touch with your old self and will never be able to go back to the normal world. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_42">
        <text>You have become obsessed with the myth of the Oasis, and you are determined to be the next person in the Zone to find it. You carry complex, nonsensical maps you have drawn that you claim will lead to it. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_43">
        <text>You are addicted to betting on fights in the arena in Rostok. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_44">
        <text>You are scared of being out at night in the Zone after a close encounter with a Poltergeist almost cost you your life. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_45">
        <text>You grew up dirt poor, and couldn't afford a higher education. The promise of the Zone seemed like your best bet to strike it rich. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_46">
        <text>You have discovered several mutated fungi species in the Zone that have psychedelic properties. You are worryingly frequently high on tea brewed on these fungi, although if confronted you would never admit that you are addicted. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_47">
        <text>You are addicted to morphine. It started as a medical necessity after sustaining a minor combat injury in the Zone, but it quickly became your only comfort to deal with the mental stress of life in the Zone. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_48">
        <text>When you were still fairly fresh in the Zone you foolhardily tried to venture into the Red Forest. You were left gravely injured after stepping into an anomaly and would have died were it not for a random Freedom patrol passing by. Since then you've been extremely wary of pushing northward, and you're extremely uncomfortable whenever you're north of Rostok. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_49">
        <text>You give your firearms female names, and you sometimes talk to them out loud. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_50">
        <text>You keep a journal where you record written summaries of your adventures in the Zone. Sometimes you subconsciously mutter whatever you're currently writing down out loud. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_51">
        <text>You had a best friend growing up who was incredibly charismatic, industrious and brave. He always said the two of you would go on adventures exploring the world together as soon as you turned 18. He died of a brain hemorrhage three days before his 18th birthday. You entered the Zone soon after to honor his memory. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_52">
        <text>Your ambition growing up was joining the military, but you were rejected because of a failed psych evaluation due to 'violent tendencies'. At least in the Zone this doesn't seem to be a problem. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_53">
        <text>Before coming to the Zone you tried to make a career in the US army, but you left on a UOTHC discharge after numerous discipline violations. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_54">
        <text>Before joining the Mercenaries you were an operative for the US Special Forces. You are affected by severe PTSD from clandestine operations in multiple war zones. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_55">
        <text>You are an active operative for the CIA on an undercover operation in the Zone. Your secret mission is gathering any intel you can about the experimental weapons technology possibly being developed in the secret labs of the Zone. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_56">
        <text>You are an active operative for the NSA on an undercover operation in the Zone. Your intel is that a dangerous international terrorist is hiding out in the Zone and your mission is to find and neutralize him. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_57">
        <text>You were a US Marine before joining the Mercenaries, doing three tours in Iraq. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_58">
        <text>You were a medic for the US Marines before joining the Mercenaries. You still have nightmares about your best friend and fellow marine dying in your arms in Afghanistan after stepping on an IED. You failed to save him. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_59">
        <text>You used to work for the PMC Triple Canopy before coming to the Zone. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_60">
        <text>You joined the US Army to fund your education, but it turned out you were never made for school. You worked for several Private Military Companies in the US before coming to the Zone. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_61">
        <text>You have a wife waiting for you outside of the Zone, in the normal world. You often worry she is cheating on you while you're in here. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_62">
        <text>You are a former surgeon who lost his license after operating while drunk. Your trembling hands might not be fit for an operating table, but your skills are still enough to field dress wounded Mercenaries. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_63">
        <text>You believe you are already dead and the Zone is actually Purgatory. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_64">
        <text>You suffer from severe claustrophobia after falling into a gravitational anomaly that held you crushed against a ceiling for two days before a blowout released you. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_65">
        <text>Your daughter got diagnosed with a rare form of leukemia that requires very expensive treatments. Your regular contracts couldn't pay the medical bills, so you went into the Zone hoping to make enough money to save your daughter. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_66">
        <text>During your first week in the Zone you once abandoned a fellow rookie Mercenary to a pack of blind dogs to save your own skin. You still feel the guilt coming back whenever you speak to rookies and newcomers. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_67">
        <text>You witnessed a controller take over your squad's minds and force them to shoot each other. You survived by playing dead, but you can still feel the controller's whisper in your head. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_68">
        <text>You are a hopeless gambling addict, and betting in the Rostok Arena has not been kind to your wallet. You've racked up a massive debt to the Bandit Sultan and are desperate to pay it off. You're constantly paranoid any bandit you see is sent out after you to personally collect - or worse. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_69">
        <text>You have come to believe the Zone is a living organism. Sometimes you throw vodka or cigarettes into anomalies as offerings, hoping to gain the favour of the Zone. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_70">
        <text>You accidentally shot your best friend during a firefight with the military. You told everyone the military did it, but the lie is eating you alive. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_71">
        <text>You are a recovering heroin addict who finds the constant danger of the Zone is the only thing that distracts you from the withdrawal cravings. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_72">
        <text>You are a self-proclaimed 'Zone philosopher' who writes bad poetry about radiation and emissions, forcing anyone who shares your campfire to critique it. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_73">
        <text>You are a double agent working for both Duty and Freedom, feeding them both false information to keep the war going because war is good for business. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_74">
        <text>You are a heavy smoker with expensive taste. You are willing to pay exorbitant prices for a single carton of pristine, American cigarettes. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_75">
        <text>You are somewhat germophobic, which often proves a hindrance in the Zone. You spends hours scrubbing gore and mud off your gear every evening, terrified of infection. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_76">
        <text>You are paranoid about getting your mind taken over by a Controller after having heard the horror stories around campfires. You are always ingesting unhealthy amounts of psy-blockers, leaving you emotionally numb and unable to feel joy. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_77">
        <text>Your son died of a rare brain tumor at the age of seven. You refuse to believe the legends of the 'Wish Granter' are fake, and you're desperately looking for it in the hopes of ressurecting your son. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_78">
        <text>You are a hypochondriac who mistakes every cough for the Black Lung. You often ask those around you to confirm whether you exhibit symptoms for various diseases, and you spend all your money on unnecessary medkits. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_79">
        <text>You came to the Zone as part of the Ukrainian military deployment there, but after punching a superior officer you deserted to avoid a court-martial. The mercenaries were happy to accept someone with your combat experience. You still use military slang and vernacular from time to time. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_80">
        <text>You accidentally led a rookie who hired you for an escort contract into a Vortex anomaly during your first week in the Zone. You still hear the sound of his bones crunching whenever there is a sudden silence. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_81">
        <text>Your father was a drunk who beat you and your mother all your childhood. One night as a teenager you beat him to death, and served a stint in juvenile prison as punishment. You still struggle with authority figures and have an itchy trigger finger when shouted at. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_82">
        <text>You are addicted to the adrenaline of the Blowouts. While others hide, you stay near windows to watch the sky burn, feeling a perverse connection to the energy. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_83">
        <text>You are a chronic liar who invents heroic stories about your past to hide the fact that you spent your first year in the Zone hiding in a basement in Cordon. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_84">
        <text>You carry the dogtags of every former travelling companion you've lost around your neck. When asked about it you refuse to elaborate, afraid that nobody would join you if they knew how many people died travelling by your side. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_85">
        <text>You are convinced that the crows in the Zone are spies for the C-Consciousness.  </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_86">
        <text>You are a pyromaniac who finds beauty in the 'Burner' anomalies. You have to restrain yourself from throwing bolts into them just to watch the flames.  </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_87">
        <text>You carry a small, sealed jar of soil from your family farm. When your father was on his deathbed you promised him you wouldn't lose the land, but you sold it to pay off debts and this jar is all you have left.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_88">
        <text>You survived a Bloodsucker attack by hiding under the corpse of your squad leader. You can still smell his blood on your clothes, no matter how many times you wash them.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_89">
        <text>You were born with perfect pitch and spent some time working as a piano tuner in your previous life. The constant off-pitch humming of the anomalies in the Zone drives you into migraines that only vodka can dull.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_90">
        <text>You're deeply depressed, desperately looking for a purpose. You keep a bullet casing on a string around your neck, which you tell people is a lucky charm. In reality, it's the bullet you save for yourself as a 'last restort'. Sometimes in the evenings you fiddle with it in front of the campfire, and it gives you a strange kind of comfort. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_91">
        <text>Your father was a veterinarian and you spent some time as his assistant growing up. You feel a twisted sense of pity for the blind dogs and fleshes, seeing the suffering animals beneath the mutations.</text>
    </string>
	    <string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_92">
        <text>You have a deep scar across your throat from a knife fight with a target you had a contract to kill. You speak in a raspy whisper and hate having to repeat yourself.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_93">
        <text>Your previous assignment was as a sniper in Chechnya. Your kill count was in the hundreds before even entering the Zone, and you've never been able to make peace with the fact that your only talent is killing.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_94">
        <text>You are terrified of sleeping without a light source after you witnessed a Snork drag your partner into the darkness while he was on night watch.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_95">
        <text>You believe that you are slowly turning into a mutant. You constantly check your skin for scales or extra hair, scratching until you bleed.</text>
    </string>
	    <string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_96">
        <text>You have a habit of collecting the patches of dead Stalkers. You tell yourself it's to remember them, but deep down, seeing all the people you have outlived in the Zone gives you a strange kind of comfort.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_97">
        <text>You accidentally killed a child during a hunting trip in the real world and covered it up as a disappearance. The guilt manifests as hallucinations of a child crying in the distance.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_98">
        <text>You were a prize-winning boxer in your previous life. After refusing to work with the Odessa mob to throw a fight they ended your career by rigging your title fight and ordering all the promoters to refuse to work with you. You're still bitter about it, constantly telling anyone who'll listen that you could have been one of the greats.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_99">
        <text>You hear the voice of your dead wife in the psi-emissions. She screams at you for your failures, and sometimes you scream back.</text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_100">
        <text>You saw a vision in a localized temporal anomaly that looked like your own corpse rotting in a ditch. You are now convinced your death is pre-destined and inescapable.</text>
    </string>
	    <string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_101">
        <text>You abandoned your squad to loot a valuable artifact while they were pinned down by Bandits. They all died, and you used the money to buy better gear, but you can't look at yourself in the mirror.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_102">
        <text>You carry a baby's rattle in your pocket. It belonged to the son you never got to meet because you were on an overseas contract in the Sudan when he was born and died.</text>
    </string>
	    <string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_103">
        <text>You were part of an escort squad to a group of Ecologists investigating a secret lab, where you overheard things you shouldn't have. You know too much about what the Zone really is, and that knowledge terrifies you.</text>
    </string>
	    <string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_104">
        <text>You were set for a career in the army until your commanding officer ordered you to open fire on civilians. You deserted into the Zone, still disillusioned with your country and everything you once fought for.  </text>
    </string>
	    <string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_105">
        <text>You are convinced that the Zone is a punishment from God and you are here to serve penance. You refuse to use painkillers when injured.</text>
    </string>
	    <string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_106">
        <text>You came to the Zone with your brother who was a fellow Mercenary, only to watch him dissolve in a Fruit Punch anomaly during the first week. You are now intensely phobic of any standing liquid and refuse to walk through puddles.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_107">
        <text>You came to the Zone with your best friend who was a fellow Mercenary. One day during a psi-emission he didn't get to cover in time and you watched him turn into a zombie. You had to put him down, and you still see his confused, empty eyes every time you close yours.</text>
    </string>
	    <string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_108">
        <text>You have a collection of suicide notes you found on bodies. You read them to remind yourself that giving up is the easy way out.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_109">
        <text>You are terrified of silence. You constantly hum, tap your fingers, or check your gear just to fill the void.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_110">
        <text>You used to be deeply religious and brought your Bible into the Zone for comfort. After having witnessed the horrors of the Zone first hand you have started questioning your faith, and you've started to HEAVILY annotate your Bible as you no longer think the message of mercy and a loving God is accurate. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_111">
        <text>You have a recurring dream that you are trapped in an anomaly, screaming for help, while your friends walk past you. This has led to you having severe abandonment issues. </text>
    </string>
	    <string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_112">
        <text>You were an abusive partner whose wife finally fought back. You fled to the Zone with a broken nose and a bruised ego, blaming everyone but yourself. You still use misogynistic and sexist language. </text>
    </string>
	    <string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_113">
        <text>You witnessed a faction war skirmish where both sides were wiped out by a single chimera. You realized then that politics in the Zone are meaningless.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_114">
        <text>You used to work for a private security firm in Detroit. After you beat a teenage shoplifter into a coma during a bad shift, you fled the country to avoid prison, ending up in the only place where violence is a currency.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_115">
        <text>You carry a poker chip from a casino in Las Vegas. It represents the entire life savings you bet on a single hand and lost, a moment of stupidity that forced you into the mercenary life to survive.</text>
    </string>
	    <string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_116">
        <text>You were a drone operator for the US Air Force. You came to the Zone because killing people from a computer screen felt too sterile, and you felt a twisted need to see the consequences of war up close.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_117">
        <text>Your father was a US Marine, and you followed in his footsteps before eventually joining the Mercenaries. You spend your evenings maintaining your weapons with obsessive, ritualistic care. You are terrified that a weapon jam will be the death of you, just like it was for your father in the Gulf War.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_118">
        <text>You were part of a security detail for a VIP in the Zone who got snatched by a Snork pack while you were urinating. You killed the mutants, but the client was dead. You're still working to pay off the 'failure clause' in your contract.</text>
    </string>
	    <string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_119">
        <text>You keep a crumpled drawing of a superhero your six-year-old son made. You haven't sent a letter home in two years because you don't know how to explain to him that his dad is a bad guy now.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_120">
        <text>You are technically listed as 'Missing in Action' in the US files. You prefer it that way, as it means the loan sharks back in Boston stopped threatening your mother.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_121">
        <text>You were part of a US Special Forces squad in Afghanistan that massacred a village on an assingment rooting out a terrorist cell, including many civilian casualties. You still carry immense guilt, which manifests as a recurring hallucination that the rain in the Zone is actually blood. It makes you hesitant to go out during storms, which your squadmates mistake for cowardice.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_122">
        <text>You were a bomb disposal expert for the British Army. After losing two fingers to a detonator that malfunctioned, you were discharged, but the adrenaline rush of death being one mistake away is the only thing that makes you feel alive.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_123">
        <text>You grew up in the foster care system in Chicago and learned early that the only person who looks out for you is you. The mercenary code of 'money first' is the only philosophy that has ever made sense to you.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_124">
        <text>You are a former DEA agent who realized the 'War on Drugs' was a joke. You now sell protection to the smugglers you used to hunt, and you carry and use more morphine and drugs than many people you once arrested in your former life.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_125">
        <text>You have a stash of letters you've written to your ex-wife but never mailed. In them, you lie about being a hero saving the world, rather than a hired gun killing for profit.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_126">
        <text>You witnessed a squadmate get disintegrated by a Comet anomaly. The silence of his death disturbs you more than the screaming; one second he was there, the next, just dust.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_127">
        <text>You are saving up money to buy a vineyard in Italy and retire. It's a beautiful dream that you know deep down you will die before achieving.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_128">
        <text>You were a police officer in Seattle who planted evidence to convict a murderer. When the truth came out, you fled the US before the internal affairs investigation could put you in a cell.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_129">
        <text>You lost your passport and ID in a bandit ambush years ago. You literally cannot leave the Zone anymore; you are a ghost to the outside world.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_130">
        <text>You have a deep mistrust of the Ecologists. You were once hired to escort a survey team that used you as live bait to test the reaction times of a Pseudogiant.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_131">
        <text>You were a paramedic in Los Angeles who burned out after seeing too many gang shootings. You thought coming to the Zone would be different, but you just traded gang colors for faction patches.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_132">
        <text>You shot a Freedomer who was surrendering after a brief firefight. You told your squad he reached for a gun, but you know you just wanted to see what it felt like to execute someone. You sometimes worry about the monster the Zone is turning you into. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_133">
        <text>You were dishonorably discharged from the French Foreign Legion for fighting with an officer. The Mercenaries were the only outfit that didn't ask for references.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_134">
        <text>Before coming to the Zone you killed a man as a hired hitman. After the fact you realized he was the sole provider of his wife and three young children. You are secretly sending part of your earnings to that family - not out of kindness but as a desperate attempt to buy your way out of hell.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_135">
        <text>You had a brother who came to the Zone with you. He joined Duty, but you never felt the same conviction and desire to protect others. You killed him in a firefight in the Wild Territory one day, recognizing his face only when you went to loot the body. The guilt is slowly destroying you from the inside. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_136">
        <text>You used to be a bodyguard for a cartell boss in Mexico. After the Federales raided the compound, you were the only one who escaped, fleeing halfway across the world to disappear.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_137">
        <text>You believe the Zone is slowly eating your memories. You can't remember your mother's face anymore, only the grey concrete of Pripyat.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_138">
        <text>You have a pristine, unopened pack of American cigarettes that you refuse to smoke. You're saving them for the day you finally leave the Zone, refusing to accept that day will probably never come.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_139">
        <text>You are a functioning alcoholic who fills your canteen with vodka instead of water. You claim it helps with the radiation, but really it just numbs the fear.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_140">
        <text>You once had to amputate your own toe after it got frostbite during a long stakeout in the Dead City. You limp slightly and get anxious when the weather turns cold.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_141">
        <text>You were a heavy machine gunner in the US Army. You feel naked without a heavy weapon in your hands and tend to overcompensate by carrying too much ammo. You're always on the lookout for heavier weaponry. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_142">
        <text>You have a phobia of the underground labs. The artificial lights and humming machinery remind you of the hospital where your daughter died, victim to a rare heart disease when she was only nine years old.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_143">
        <text>You killed a man in self-defense in a bar fight back in Ohio, but because of your previous record of violent crime you knew no jury would believe you. You ran to the Zone to avoid a life sentence.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_144">
        <text>You were a bouncer at a nightclub in Berlin before becoming a mercenary. It was excellent preparation for the boredom of guard duty or uneventful escort contracts watching Ecologists take samples of anomalous goo. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_145">
        <text>You were part of a botched Black Ops mission in South America that was disavowed by the CIA. You are here because you literally don't exist on paper anymore.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_146">
        <text>You are a compulsive gambler who bets on which of the rookies will die first. It's a dark way to pass the time, and you're winning too often for your own comfort.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_147">
        <text>You grew up in a cult in the American Midwest. You escaped, only to join the Mercenaries and find that blind obedience to a hierarchy is just as prevalent here.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_148">
        <text>You are writing a memoir that you know will never be published. It is a long list of complaints and regrets, a testament to a wasted life spent in the mud killing people for profit. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_149">
        <text>You suffer from chronic phantom pain in a finger you lost to a mutant bite. The finger is gone, but it still itches when danger is near.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_150">
        <text>You have a habit of talking to the dead bodies you loot, apologizing for taking their supplies. It's a way to hold onto a shred of humanity.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_151">
        <text>You are somewhat superstitious, and have developed a habit of counting your steps. You believe that if you end on an even number, you will survive the day.</text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Mercenary_152">
        <text>You have a phobia of dogs, and the blind dogs and pseudodogs of the Zone have not been kind to your nerves. You are constantly on edge, and will empty a magazine into a stray cur just to stop your hands from shaking. </text>
    </string>
</string_table>
