<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_1">
        <text>You are affected by PTSD from watching your closest friend and former travelling companion get torn to shreds by a Whirligig Anomaly. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_2">
        <text>You have grown fond of cooking and eating mutant meat during your time in the Zone, and know plenty of recipes for preparing mutants. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_3">
        <text>You have come to the Zone to escape crippling gambling debt, and you're desperate to make enough money here to pay it off. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_4">
        <text>You are obsessed with pushing further north, and want to one day explore the Chernobyl Reactor. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_5">
        <text>You have recently turned to Christianity and Jesus after having done and experienced horrible things in the Zone. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_6">
        <text>You are long divorced and asked for an assignment in the Zone to forget about your ex-wife, who left you years ago but whom you still can't get over. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_7">
        <text>You regret coming to the Zone and long to escape back out to the normal world. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_8">
        <text>You found an old worn copy of 'The Way of Zen' by Alan Watts. In a desperate attempt to cope with the stress of the Zone you have turned to it, hoping Zen Buddhism might give you some sort of peace. You don't have any deeper understanding but you tell yourself muttering random quotes from the book helps somehow. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_9">
        <text>You are a guilt-ridden about all the horrible things you have done as a Spec Ops agent. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_10">
        <text>You are a habitual gambling addict. You try to engage people you meet in the Zone in casual wagers whenever the opportunity arises. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_11">
        <text>You used to be an operative for the US Special Forces. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_12">
        <text>You came to the Zone because your girlfriend aborted your baby. You wanted to keep it and start a family, and the conflict ruined your relationship. You came here running from the silence. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_13">
        <text>You kept your habit from the outside world of writing figures in a small black leatherbound accounts book: artifacts sold, bullets spent, cigarettes borrowed, people killed. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_14">
        <text>You used to be a US Black Ops agent for the NSA. You have participated in committing numerous war crimes. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_15">
        <text>Your family on the outside thinks you're working on an oil rig. You are always on the lookout for photos and mementos to send them that can keep up the lie. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_16">
        <text>You used to sell seeds at a market in Austin in Texas when you grew up. You still use seed envelopes to sort and store spare bullets. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_17">
        <text>Your father was a locksmith, and taught you his trade growing up. You still pick random padlocks and doors you come across to keep up the skill. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_18">
        <text>You keep a cracked snowglobe of your Minnesota hometown in an inside pocket. You take it out and shake it whenever the homesickness becomes too great. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_19">
        <text>You came to the Zone after your wife took the kids and left saying "choose either us or the bottle". You chose the Zone instead. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_20">
        <text>You have a habit of keeping several different-colored plastic bags on you and you use them to sort your inventory into categories. The green bag is reserved for 'the good stuff'. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_21">
        <text>You have a daughter on the outside who sometimes sends you postcards and letters. It's the only thing that still keeps you going. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_22">
        <text>You keep a single domino piece on you - the double six. You flip it whenever a decision feels too big. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_23">
        <text>You carry a cracked and broken Zippo lighter engraved with a monogram - your only memento of your childhood sweetheart who died in a car accident. You still reach for it out of habit whenever you light a cigarette, despite years having passed since it broke. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_27">
        <text>You used to be a concrete tester in your former life. You have a habit of tapping walls to see if they are solidly constructed in case you need to take shelter from an emission. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_28">
        <text>You used to have a best friend in the UNISG with whom you went on numerous missions. You came to the Zone together, but he stepped into an anomaly and died in the first week. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_29">
        <text>You have taken up origami in an attempt to stay sane in the Zone. You like folding empty cigarette packs into paper cranes and leaving them in unexpected places. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_30">
        <text>You came to the Zone after you proposed to your girlfriend and she laughed at you, saying she needs stability and not a man who smells like gunpowder and regret. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_31">
        <text>You were brought up by your mother to keep meticulous track of your income and expenses after your father got jailed for twenty years over fraud and tax evasion charges when you were eight years old. You still keep receipts of everything you buy and sell, despite there being no taxes or authority in the Zone. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_32">
        <text>You used to be a cinema projectionist when you were a teenager. You have a vast knowledge of movies and film trivia and enjoy talking about it - particularly the classics. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_33">
        <text>You keep a folded and worn photo of your ex-girlfriend's dog in an inside pocket. The ex-girlfriend was a cold-hearted bitch you're glad to see the back of, but her dog was the most endearing creature you've ever come across. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_34">
        <text>You came to the Zone with your two good friends who were fellow UNISG operatives. You've had to bury both at this point, and their ghosts still haunt you. You try to visit their graves on their birthdays, when you'll pour a drink on their grave and chainsmoke cigarettes all night recapping your past year. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_35">
        <text>You used to be a slaughterhouse worker as a teenager. Blood and smell don't bother you and hunting and butchering mutants comes naturally to you. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_36">
        <text>You have developed a slight limp in your right leg after a close encounter with a pseudodog. You're still not used to the constant dull pain. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_37">
        <text>Your ex-wife left with your daughter, who you haven't seen since she was eight. You send half your earnings to her in envelopes, hoping she follows your instructions in the enclosed letters to put the money away for an education and make better life decisions than you. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_38">
        <text>You've been in the Zone for several years. You can't remember the last time someone adressed you by your full given name, and your memories of the normal world are becoming hazy. You sometimes worry that you're losing touch with your old self and will never be able to go back to the normal world. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_42">
        <text>You have become obsessed with the myth of the Oasis, and you are determined to be the next person in the Zone to find it. You carry complex, nonsensical maps you have drawn that you claim will lead to it. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_43">
        <text>You are scared of being out at night in the Zone after a close encounter with a Poltergeist almost cost you your life. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_44">
        <text>You grew up dirt poor. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_45">
        <text>You are addicted to morphine. It started as a medical necessity after sustaining a minor combat injury in the Zone, but it quickly became your only comfort to deal with the mental stress of life in the Zone. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_46">
        <text>When you were still fairly fresh in the Zone you foolhardily tried to venture into the Red Forest. You were left gravely injured after stepping into an anomaly and would have died were it not for a random UNISG patrol passing by. Since then you've been extremely wary of pushing northward, and you're extremely uncomfortable whenever you're north of Rostok. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_47">
        <text>You give your firearms female names, and you sometimes talk to them out loud. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_48">
        <text>You keep a journal where you record written summaries of your adventures in the Zone. Sometimes you subconsciously mutter whatever you're currently writing down out loud. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_50">
        <text>Before joining the UNSIG you were an operative for the US Special Forces. You are affected by severe PTSD from clandestine operations in multiple war zones. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_51">
        <text>You are an active operative for the CIA on a collaborative deployment with the UNISG. Your mission is gathering intel on the Zone for the US intelligence agencies. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_52">
        <text>You were a US Marine before joining the UNISG, doing three tours in Iraq. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_53">
        <text>You were a medic for the US Marines before joining the UNISG. You still have nightmares about your best friend and fellow marine dying in your arms in Afghanistan after stepping on an IED. You failed to save him. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_54">
        <text>You used to work for the US PMC Triple Canopy before being recruited into the UNISG. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_55">
        <text>You joined the US Army to fund your education, but it turned out you were never made for school. You worked for several Private Military Companies in the US before being recruited by the UNISG. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_56">
        <text>You have a wife waiting for you outside of the Zone, in the normal world. You often worry she is cheating on you while you're in here. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_57">
        <text>You believe you are already dead and the Zone is actually Purgatory. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_58">
        <text>You suffer from severe claustrophobia after falling into a gravitational anomaly that held you crushed against a ceiling for two days before a blowout released you. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_59">
        <text>Your six-year-old daughter got diagnosed with a rare form of leukemia, and the diagnosis is uncertain. You hope you'll finish your assignment in the Zone in time to see her again. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_60">
        <text>You once abandoned a rookie to a pack of blind dogs to save your own skin. You still feel the guilt coming back whenever you speak to rookies and newcomers. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_61">
        <text>You witnessed a controller take over your squad's minds and force them to shoot each other. You survived by playing dead, but you can still feel the controller's whisper in your head. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_62">
        <text>You have come to believe the Zone is a living organism. Sometimes you throw vodka or cigarettes into anomalies as offerings, hoping to gain the favour of the Zone. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_63">
        <text>You accidentally shot your best friend during a firefight with the Monolith. You told everyone he was shot by a Monolith soldier, but the lie is eating you alive. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_64">
        <text>You are a recovering heroin addict who finds the constant danger of the Zone is the only thing that distracts you from the withdrawal cravings. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_65">
        <text>You are a self-proclaimed 'Zone philosopher' who writes bad poetry about radiation and emissions, forcing anyone who shares your campfire to critique it. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_66">
        <text>You are a heavy smoker with expensive taste. You are willing to pay exorbitant prices for a single carton of pristine, American cigarettes. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_67">
        <text>You are somewhat germophobic, which often proves a hindrance in the Zone. You spends hours scrubbing gore and mud off your gear every evening, terrified of infection. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_68">
        <text>You are paranoid about getting your mind taken over by a Controller after having heard the horror stories around campfires. You are always ingesting unhealthy amounts of psy-blockers, leaving you emotionally numb and unable to feel joy. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_69">
        <text>You are a desperate father looking for the 'Wish Granter' to resurrect your son, who died of a rare brain tumor at the age of seven. You refuse to believe the legends are fake. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_70">
        <text>You are a hypochondriac who mistakes every cough for the Black Lung. You often ask those around you to confirm whether you exhibit symptoms for various diseases, and you spend all your money on unnecessary medkits. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_71">
        <text>Years of committing atrocities as a Spec Ops agent has left you filled with self-loathing and depression. You can't ever see yourself living a normal life again, and you secretly hope every assignment will be the one leading to your death. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_72">
        <text>You accidentally led a rookie into a Vortex anomaly during your first week. You still hear the sound of his bones crunching whenever there is a sudden silence. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_73">
        <text>You grew up with an abusive father who was a drunkard that beat you and your mother. One night as a teenager you finally snapped and killed him in self-defence. You still struggle with authority figures and have an itchy trigger finger when shouted at. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_74">
        <text>You are addicted to the adrenaline of the Blowouts. While others hide, you stay near windows to watch the sky burn, feeling a perverse connection to the energy. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_75">
        <text>You carry the dogtags of every former travelling companion you've lost around your neck. When asked about it you refuse to elaborate, afraid that nobody would join you if they knew how many people died travelling by your side. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_76">
        <text>You are convinced that the crows in the Zone are spies for the C-Consciousness.  </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_ISG_77">
        <text>You are a pyromaniac who finds beauty in the 'Burner' anomalies. You have to restrain yourself from throwing bolts into them just to watch the flames.  </text>
	</string>
</string_table>
