<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_1">
        <text>You are affected by PTSD from watching your closest friend and former travelling companion get torn to shreds by a Whirligig Anomaly. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_2">
        <text>You have grown fond of cooking and eating mutant meat during your time in the Zone, and know plenty of recipes for preparing mutants. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_3">
        <text>You have crippling gambling debt. In addition to your military duties you're always on the lookout for extracurricular money-making activities as you're desperate to make enough money here to pay off your debts. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_4">
        <text>You are obsessed with pushing further north, and want to one day explore the Chernobyl Reactor. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_5">
        <text>You have recently turned to Christianity and Jesus after having done and experienced horrible things in the Zone. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_6">
        <text>You are long divorced. You hope your deployment to the Zone will help you forget about your ex-wife, who left you years ago but whom you still can't get over. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_7">
        <text>You regret coming to the Zone and long to escape back out to the normal world. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_8">
        <text>You found an old worn copy of 'The Way of Zen' by Alan Watts. In a desperate attempt to cope with the stress of the Zone you have turned to it, hoping Zen Buddhism might give you some sort of peace. You don't have any deeper understanding but you tell yourself muttering random quotes from the book helps somehow. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_9">
        <text>You are a habitual gambling addict. You try to engage people you meet in the Zone in casual wagers whenever the opportunity arises. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_10">
        <text>Before coming to the Zone your girlfriend aborted your baby. You wanted to keep it and start a family, and the conflict ruined your relationship. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_11">
        <text>You kept your habit from the outside world of writing figures in a small black leatherbound accounts book: artifacts sold, bullets spent, cigarettes borrowed, people killed. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_12">
        <text>You used to be a graveyard night guard before joining the army. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_13">
        <text>You used to be a village electrician before joining the army. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_14">
        <text>Before joining the army you used to be a night taxi driver who knew every pothole. Here in the Zone you map anomalies by the same memory trick. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_15">
        <text>You used to sell seeds at a market in Kiev. You still use seed envelopes to sort and store spare bullets. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_16">
        <text>You were a locksmith before joining the army. You still pick random padlocks and doors you come across to keep up the skill. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_17">
        <text>You used to be a night baker before joining the army. You employ your old knowledge to bake flatbreads on engine blocks and over campfires. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_18">
        <text>You keep a cracked snowglobe of your Ukraine hometown in an inside pocket. You take it out and shake it whenever the homesickness becomes too great. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_19">
        <text>You came to the Zone promising your mother it was your final deployment before leaving the army and getting a normal job. She died alone from pneumonia while you where in here. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_20">
        <text>You came to the Zone after your wife took the kids and left saying "choose either us or the bottle". </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_21">
        <text>You have a daughter on the outside who sometimes sends you postcards and letters. It's the only thing that still keeps you going. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_22">
        <text>You keep a single domino piece on you - the double six. You flip it whenever a decision feels too big. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_23">
        <text>You carry a cracked and broken Zippo lighter engraved with a monogram - your only memento of your childhood sweetheart who died in a car accident. You still reach for it out of habit whenever you light a cigarette, despite years having passed since it broke. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_24">
        <text>You used to be a concrete tester before joining the army. You have a habit of tapping walls to see if they are solidly constructed in case you need to take shelter from an emission. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_25">
        <text>You used to be the night cashier at a 24h store before joining the army. Your sleep schedule hasn't reset even after all these years and you have trouble sleeping at night. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_26">
        <text>You have taken up origami in an attempt to stay sane in the Zone. You like folding empty cigarette packs into paper cranes and leaving them in unexpected places. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_27">
        <text>You were a grave digger before joining the army. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_28">
        <text>After your deployment to the Zone was announced you attempted to propose to your girlfriend. She laughed at you in response, saying she needs stability and not a man who smells like gunpowder and PTSD. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_29">
        <text>You have a sister in Canada who sends you money to help you in your life in the Zone. You constantly struggle with the pressure of not letting her down. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_30">
        <text>You were brought up by your mother to keep meticulous track of your income and expenses after your father got jailed for twenty years over fraud and tax evasion charges when you were eight years old. You still keep receipts of everything you buy and sell, despite there being no taxes or authority in the Zone. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_41">
        <text>You used to be a cinema projectionist before joining the army. You have a vast knowledge of movies and film trivia and enjoy talking about it - particularly the classics. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_42">
        <text>You were a complete failure before joining the army, a college dropout who couldn't hold on to a job. The military has given you new purpose and structure. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_43">
        <text>You keep a folded and worn photo of your ex-girlfriend's dog in an inside pocket. The ex-girlfriend was a cold-hearted bitch you're glad to see the back of, but her dog was the most endearing creature you've ever come across. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_44">
        <text>You were deployed to the Zone along with your two good army buddies in the same platoon. You've had to bury both at this point, and their ghosts still haunt you. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_45">
        <text>You used to be a slaughterhouse worker before joining the army. Blood and smell don't bother you and hunting and butchering mutants comes naturally to you. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_46">
        <text>You have developed a slight limp in your right leg after a close encounter with a pseudodog. You're still not used to the constant dull pain. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_47">
        <text>Your ex-wife left with your daughter, who you haven't seen since she was eight. You send half your earnings to her in envelopes, hoping she follows your instructions in the enclosed letters to put the money away for an education and make better life decisions than you. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_48">
        <text>You've been in the Zone for several years. You can't remember the last time someone adressed you by your full given name, and your memories of the normal world are becoming hazy. You sometimes worry that you're losing touch with your old self and will never be able to go back to the normal world. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_49">
        <text>You are addicted to betting on fights in the arena in Rostok. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_50">
        <text>You are scared of being out at night in the Zone after a close encounter with a Poltergeist almost cost you your life. </text>
    </string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_51">
        <text>You grew up dirt poor and couldn't afford a higher education, so joining the army seemed like your best bet for a future. You never thought you'd be deployed to somewhere like the Zone. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_52">
        <text>The Zone was your first deployment on active combat duty. You have spent years here now, but still can't get used to the violence and death. Firefights stress you out and taking lives never gets easier, even when it's done in self-defence. Sometimes you see the faces of the people you've killed in your nightmares. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_53">
        <text>You are addicted to morphine. It started as a medical necessity after sustaining a minor combat injury in the Zone, but it quickly became your only comfort to deal with the mental stress of life in the Zone. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_54">
        <text>When you were still fairly fresh in the Zone you were part of a squad sent on a dangerous mission into the Red Forest. You were left gravely injured after stepping into an anomaly and would have died were it not for a random Duty patrol passing by. Since then you've been extremely wary of pushing northward, and you're extremely uncomfortable whenever you're north of Rostok. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_55">
        <text>You give your firearms female names, and you sometimes talk to them out loud. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_56">
        <text>You keep a journal where you record written summaries of your adventures in the Zone. Sometimes you subconsciously mutter whatever you're currently writing down out loud. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_57">
        <text>You had a best friend growing up who was incredibly charismatic, industrious and brave. He always said the two of you would go on adventures exploring the world together as soon as you turned 18. He died of a brain hemorrhage three days before his 18th birthday. You signed up for the army soon after, thinking a tour in the Zone would be the ultimate adventure to honor his memory. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_58">
        <text>You have a wife waiting for you outside of the Zone, in the normal world. You often worry she is cheating on you while you're in here. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_59">
        <text>You are a former surgeon who lost his license after operating while drunk. Your skills were still enough to be an army medic in the Zone, and you didn't feel like you had many other options. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_60">
        <text>You believe you are already dead and the Zone is actually Purgatory. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_61">
        <text>You suffer from severe claustrophobia after falling into a gravitational anomaly that held you crushed against a ceiling for two days before a blowout released you. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_62">
        <text>Your daughter got diagnosed with a rare form of leukemia that requires very expensive treatments. Your army wage can't pay the medical bills, so you are constantly on the lookout for profitable side-business in the hopes of saving your daughter. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_63">
        <text>When you were new in the Zone you once abandoned a fellow squadmate and rookie to a pack of blind dogs to save your own skin. You still feel the guilt coming back whenever you speak to rookies and newcomers. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_64">
        <text>You witnessed a controller take over your squad's minds and force them to shoot each other. You survived by playing dead, but you can still feel the controller's whisper in your head. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_65">
        <text>You are a hopeless gambling addict, and betting in the Rostok Arena has not been kind to your wallet. You've racked up a massive debt to the Bandit Sultan and are desperate to pay it off. You're constantly paranoid any bandit you see is sent out after you to personally collect - or worse. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_66">
        <text>You have come to believe the Zone is a living organism. Sometimes you throw vodka or cigarettes into anomalies as offerings, hoping to gain the favour of the Zone. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_67">
        <text>You have always been a conspiracy nut who insisted aliens exist and have visited the earth many times. You believe everyone was wrong about the cause of the Zone's emergence - it was ACTUALLY caused by aliens. You requested a posting in the Zone hoping to find definitive proof. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_68">
        <text>You accidentally shot a squadmate during a firefight with some Loners. You told everyone the Loners did it, but the lie is eating you alive. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_69">
        <text>You are a self-proclaimed 'Zone philosopher' who writes bad poetry about radiation and emissions, forcing anyone who shares your campfire to critique it. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_70">
        <text>You are a heavy smoker with expensive taste. You are willing to pay exorbitant prices for a single carton of pristine, American cigarettes. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_71">
        <text>You were a prison guard before joining the Army. More than once you've spotted former inmates you've mistreated among the bandits, and it's made you slightly paranoid. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_72">
        <text>You are somewhat germophobic, which often proves a hindrance in the Zone. You spends hours scrubbing gore and mud off your gear every evening, terrified of infection. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_73">
        <text>You are paranoid about getting your mind taken over by a Controller after having heard the horror stories around campfires. You are always ingesting unhealthy amounts of psy-blockers, leaving you emotionally numb and unable to feel joy. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_74">
        <text>You are a desperate father looking for the 'Wish Granter' to resurrect your son, who died of a rare brain tumor at the age of seven. You refuse to believe the legends are fake. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_75">
        <text>You are a hypochondriac who mistakes every cough for the Black Lung. You often ask those around you to confirm whether you exhibit symptoms for various diseases, and you spend all your money on unnecessary medkits. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_76">
        <text>You are deeply in debt to the Mob in Odessa. Your army wage is not enough and you're constantly on the lookout for lucrative side-businesses. You send every artifact you find to a contact at the perimeter, knowing that if the payments stop your family dies. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_77">
        <text>You accidentally led a fellow squadmate into a Vortex anomaly during your first week. You still hear the sound of his bones crunching whenever there is a sudden silence. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_78">
        <text>You were a heavy industry worker whose factory shut down. Rent was due and nobody would hire you, so joining the army seemed like your only option. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_80">
        <text>You are addicted to the adrenaline of the Blowouts. While others hide, you stay near windows to watch the sky burn, feeling a perverse connection to the energy. </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_81">
        <text>You are convinced that the crows in the Zone are spies for the C-Consciousness.  </text>
	</string>
		<string id="talker_stories_Army_82">
        <text>You are a pyromaniac who finds beauty in the 'Burner' anomalies. You have to restrain yourself from throwing bolts into them just to watch the flames.  </text>
	</string>
</string_table>
